Thanks to your bold leadership and the designation of Antifa as a terrorist organization, which
is exactly what they are, Americans will no longer tolerate their unhinged violence.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Pam.
Christine.
Well, thank you, Mr. President, and thank you for hosting today and focusing on Antifa
and the terrorists that they are.
Let's not make any mistake.
These individuals do not just want to threaten our law enforcement officers, threaten our
journalists, and the citizens of this country.
They want to kill them.
Their agenda is to destroy the American people in our way of life, and this president is
standing in their way.
He is stopping them from bringing their death and their destruction to the individual citizens
in this country that just want to raise their kids and their grandkids in peace and in safety.
I want to also thank everyone around this table for being so bold and so brave, for
standing up and recognizing the threat that Antifa is to our way of life.
By recognizing how advanced they are, how sophisticated their networks are, how they've
infiltrated our entire country, and we're seeing them play out with their tactics from
city to city, and how they have built out their funding mechanisms, and sir, I also
want to thank our Treasury Secretary for his work in getting to the bottom of these funding
mechanisms and individuals who are perpetuating this violence on our American cities.
I was in Portland yesterday and had the chance to visit with the governor of Oregon and also
the mayor.
They're in town and they are absolutely covering up the terrorism that is hitting their streets.
While you talked about some of the stories of our ICE agents, our Border Patrol agents,
how they have been attacked, how they have been shot at, injured, the damage that they've
done, these leaders in these local cities, along with Pritzker and Johnson, ignore what's
going on, or sir, they're helping Antifa cover it up.
We have arrested dozens of individuals that are Antifa members or affiliated with them,
and I want to thank our Attorney General for prosecuting them and making sure they never
see the light of day again.
They have been so bold in making sure we're bringing those individuals to justice.
One of the individuals we arrested recently in Portland was the girlfriend of one of the
founders of Antifa, and that we are hoping that as we go after her, interview her, and
prosecute her, we will get more and more information about the network and how we can root them
out and eliminate them from the existence of American society.
I want to thank the new journalists here today for telling their stories and for being able
and willing to go to the streets and to cover what's happening here in America.
Many times the legacy media has looked the other way, refused to tell the stories.
The networks have not really focused on what this is and what damage it is doing to our
country and how this network of Antifa is just as sophisticated as MS-13, as TDA, as
ISIS, as Hezbollah, as Hamas, as all of them.
They are just as dangerous.
They have an agenda to destroy us, just like the other terrorists we've dealt with for
many, many years.
And today is the day that we have a president that won't tolerate it and will stand up and
fight for the American people.
So thank you for being here, for being so bold and for standing in the gap at such a
time as this.
It will matter.
And the fact that you can make a difference in your life will be one of significance because
of what you've done today.
So with that, God bless you.
And thank you, Mr. President.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Cash, please.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Mr. President, the American people gave you a sweeping mandate in your victory in this
election cycle, and they demanded safety and security for our citizens.
And your administration, with your leadership, has provided us with the resources that we
need, which is a whole-of-government approach to go after criminals absolutely everywhere,
not just outside of this country, but within this country.
And that takes a whole-of-government approach.
The interagency seated up here with the Department of Homeland Security, our Attorney General,
Deputy Attorney General, and your White House staffers, including Stephen Miller's leadership,
has allowed us to go out there and map out these networks.
What we are doing at the FBI is simple.
It does not require rocket science.
We are following the money.
Money never lies.
And that's what it's going to take to bring down this network of organized criminal thugs,
gangbangers, and, yes, domestic terrorists, because that's what they are.
They are harming everyday citizens in every single one of our communities.
And the folks you see here on the right and left, they're some of the bravest men and
women we have today.
They're reporting the stories live time, because the mainstream media won't cover it.
They're putting their lives on the line.
They're standing up for the flag.
The least we can do is stand up for them.
So you have my thanks.
I read more of your stories than I do theirs, because you guys are putting out the truth.
And we deserve a country where you are protected as equally as they are.
We in this FBI will go after the criminals with a vengeance.
We will not rest until we find every single seed, money, donor, organization, and funding
mechanism that we have.
And I want to echo the Secretary's comments on Scott Besson, who's allowing us to map
out these networks through their financial criminal activities, which has been going
on for decades.
And I would like to remind the American public, they built this disease temple of corruption
over decades.
And in eight short months, Mr. President, you have crippled their foundation because
of your leadership here, because of the interagency, because of people like Deputy Attorney General
Blanche, and because of Attorney General Pam Bondi's fearless leadership to go after criminals
wherever they are.
They will not be able to hide.
They were able to hide and conspire with prior administrations, and we are exposing their
corruption from within.
And we will go to every single city in this country under Operation Summer Heat and the
other operations we are doing at the FBI to bring these criminals to justice.
We will arrest every single one of them from whatever perch you sit in, private or public,
no matter how high your goal or your ambition is, it will be crushed by the Constitution
because the American people deserve law and order.
And that's what we're going to give you.
Thank you very much, Kesh.
Great job.